<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Smart Guide Tour System</string>


    <string name="title_activity_welcome">Home Screen</string>
    <string name="next">NEXT</string>
    <string name="skip">SKIP</string>
    <string name="start">GOT IT</string>

    <string name="slide_1_title">Hello!</string>
    <string name="slide_1_desc">Here represent as a Guide for travelling</string>

    <string name="slide_2_title">Favorite Destination</string>
    <string name="slide_2_desc">To know the favorite destination in each state and easiest way to understand the language</string>

    <string name="slide_3_title">Fare</string>
    <string name="slide_3_desc">Calculate travelling expence from one place to another in each place</string>

    <string name="slide_4_title">Map</string>
    <string name="slide_4_desc">Using Map easy to find places and shortest path in between two places and To know near by Schools,Hospitals,Restaurants.etc</string>

    <string name="play_again_desc">To see the welcome slider again, goto Settings -> apps -> welcome slider -> clear data</string>
    <string name="play_again">Play Again</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home_page1">HomePage</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Smart Guide Tourist System</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">travelguide@venturetech.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="speech_not_supported">Sorry! Your device doesn\'t support speech input</string>
    <string name="speech_prompt">Say something&#8230;</string>
    <string name="speech1">say somthing</string>

    <!--Kerala Details!-->

    <string name="kochi">Kochi also known as Cochin is a major port city on the south-west coast of India bordering
                         the Laccadive Sea.It is part of the district of Ernakulam in the state of Kerala and is
                         often referred to as Ernakulam.</string>
    <string name="varkala">Varkala is a coastal town and municipality in Thiruvananthapuram district situated in
                          the Indian state of Kerala. It is the suburban town of Thiruvananthapuram (Trivandrum city).
                          It is located 50 kilometres (approx. 32 miles) north-west of Thiruvananthapuram (Trivandrum)
                          and 37 km south-west of Kollam. Varkala Maithanam.</string>
    <string name="munnar">Sprawling tea plantations surround the serene hills of Munnar, which attract adventure travellers
                         hungry for paragliding, treks to Anaimudi (South India\'s highest peak) and hikes originating at the
                         confluence of three mountain streams.</string>
    <string name="vagamon">Vagamon, also spelt Wagamon, is a hill station located in Meenachil taluk and Kanjirappally taluk
                          of Kottayam district and Peerumade taluk of Idukki district of the state of Kerala, India. Contents.</string>
    <string name="ponmudi">Ponmudi (the Golden Peak) is a hill station in the Thiruvananthapuram District of Kerala in India.
                           It is located 55.2 km north-east of Trivandrum City at an altitude of 1100 m. Ponmudi (Varayadumotta)
                           peak is a part of the Western Ghats mountain range that runs parallel to the Arabian Sea.</string>
    <string name="vembanad">Vembanad is the second largest lagoon in India, and the lagoon lake in the state of Kerala. Spanning
                           several districts in the state of Kerala, it is known as vembanadu Lake in Kottayam Punnamada Lake in
                           Kuttanad, Kochi Lake in Kochi. Several groups of small islands including Vypin, Mulavukad, Vallarpadam,
                           Willingdon</string>
    <string name="ashtamudi">Ashtamudi Lake (Ashtamudi Kayal), in the Kollam District of the Indian state of Kerala, is the most
                            visited backwater and lake in the state. It possesses a unique wetland ecosystem and a large palm-shaped
                            water body, second only in size to the Vembanad estuary ecosystem of the state.</string>

    <string name="nelliyam">Privately owned hotels and resorts are located at various points, as one goes up the hills of Nelliyampathy.
                           The bio-farms located here are a major landmark as one proceeds up before reaching the topmost point at
                           Palagapandi Estate. The estate has a quaint bungalow, built during the British rule in India, </string>


    <!--goa details!-->
    <string name="BagaBeach">The most popular beach of Goa, Baga is located close to Calangute beach, around 30 Km
                             North of Panaji. Along with Calangute, Baga Beach is also popular for its nightlife with
                             some very famous clubs right there such as Brittos, Titos and Mambo. </string>
    <string name="CalanguteBeach">Calangute is a largest beach in north Goa and thus is known as Queens of beaches.
                                 Situated 15 kms from the capital city of Panaji, this expansive stretch of water attracts
                                 tourist from all around the globe owing to its festive and entrancing environ.</string>
    <string name="Palolembeach">Palolem Beach, located in the South Goa is one of the most beautiful beaches of the Union
                               Territory has to offer.Mostly unspoiled, the beach is often flocked with foreign tourists.</string>
    <string name="Anjunabeach">Known for its unparalleled natural beauty, glowing soft white sand and swaying palms, Anjuna Beach is a hot spot
                            for tourists both domestic and foreign. </string>
    <string name="BasilicaofBomJesus">This historic church is located in Goa and is a UNESCO World Heritage Site. The Basilica of Bom Jesus
                           houses the tomb and remains of St. Francis Xavier. Even after 400 years, the remains are in a good condition and
                           are taken out once every decade.</string>
    <string name="Cruise">The exotic beaches of Goa, pristine waters and breath taking view of sunset and sun rise can be best enjoyed through
                          the luring river cruise. </string>
    <string name="DudhsagarWaterfalls">Literally meaning milky water waterfalls because of the color of the falls, this is one of the highest
                              waterfalls in India and cascades through four-tiers.</string>
    <string name="FortAguada">The fort was built in 1612 to watch and guard against the Dutch and the Marathas. It was a reference point for the
                              vessels coming from Europe. This old Portuguese fortification stands on the beach south of Candolim, at the shore
                              of the Mandovi River.</string>


    <!--mumbai details!-->
    <string name="MarineDrive">Starting from the north of Nariman Point and ending at the famous Chowpatty beach, the Marine Drive is a 3km long
                           arc shaped road along the sea coast of South Mumbai. The coast lines the Arabian sea and is the best place to watch
                           the sunset in Mumbai.</string>
    <string name="GatewayofIndia">One of the most distinguished monument in Mumbai, The Gateway of India was built in 1924. Now it has become
                           a popular tourist hub in the city. Located at Apollo Bunder Waterfront, the monument overlooks the Arabian Sea in
                           the most beautiful way.</string>
    <string name="Juhubeach">The most popular beach in Mumbai, Juhu beach is located close to Andheri and was once quite a beautiful beach.
                           However, with so many tourists coming in here, the place has become dirty and water is also not clean because
                           of affluents from nearby factories and industries.</string>
    <string name="ColabaCauseway">One of the most crowded and electrifying places to visit in Mumbai is the Colaba Causeway, famous
                           for being a shopping paradise and having endless shops to choose from. </string>
    <string name="HajiAliDargah">Situated at the backdrop of a beautiful view of the sea is the shrine of Haji Ali, a wealthy merchant
                           turned into Muslim Sufi. People from all walks of life and religions come here to seek blessings.</string>
    <string name="BandraWorliSeaLink">Spanning across the arc of Mumbai coastline, this sea link is a civil engineering wonder that
                           reflects the modern infrastructure of the city of Mumbai.</string>
    <string name="NationalGalleryofModernArt">Situated in Colaba, Southern Mumbai, the National Gallery of Modern Art was established
                           in 1996, with an objective to promote modern trends in the Indian culture. Initially a concert venue, the
                           structure was later converted into an art gallery in 1954. </string>
    <string name="MumbaiZoo">Popularly known as Veermata Jijabai Udhyan, the zoo is the best way to spend family holidays amidst
                           a vast variety of birds and animals.</string>


    <!--kolkata details!-->
    <string name="VictoriaMemorial">The Victoria Memorial is a large marble building, which is considered to be the pride of Kolkata. Built between 1906 and 1921,
                                    it is dedicated to the memory of Queen Victoria. </string>
    <string name="FortWilliam">Fort William is a fort built in Kolkata on the eastern banks of the River Hooghly, the major distributary of Ganges, during the
                              early years of the Bengal Presidency in the British India. It was named after King William III of England and Ireland and King
                              William II of Scotland.</string>
    <string name="EdenGardens">Popular as the largest cricket stadium in the India and the second largest in the world,
                              the Eden Gardens can seat 66,000 spectators.</string>
    <string name="IndianMuseum">The Indian Museum is one of the oldest museums of the world boasting some of the most exquisite collections of ornaments,
                              fossils, skeletons, antiques, armors, mummies and stunning Mughal paintings.</string>
    <string name="Tajpur">One of the most secluded beaches of the country and one of the newest entrant in the tourism scene of West Bengal,
                         Tajpur is slowly carving out a niche for itself as the stopover destination between the two
                         major centers Digha and Shankarpur.</string>
    <string name="NakhodaMosque">Placed in the Chitpur area in the Burrabazar business district, Nakhoda mosque is one of the busiest
                         Mosques of Kolkata and dates back almost a century. </string>
    <string name="AliporeZoo">The Alipore Zoo, also known as the Calcutta Zoo or the Zoological Garden of Alipore, is the oldest zoological
                         park to have been established in India and is a major tourist attraction in Kolkata.</string>
    <string name="KalighatTemple">Kalighat Temple, one of the 51 Shakti Sthals of India, is one of the most visited Kali temples in India. The spot
                         is where the toes of Sati\'s right foot fell during Shiva\'s Rudra Taandav naach.</string>


    <!--delhi details!-->
    <string name="TheRedFort">Red fort an UNESCO Heritage monument.  It was built by mughal emperor shah jahan in the year of 1648,
                                  who also built the Taj Mahal in Agra. </string>
    <string name="HumayunTomb">Our next attraction is a heritage monument – Humayun\’s tomb and is among the must places to visit in
                                   Delhi for tourists.  Humayun\’s wife, Hamida Banu, or Hazi Begum, was instrumental behind the construction
                                   of this magnificent tomb.The tomb took 14 years to construct.</string>
    <string name="QutabMinar">Our next attraction is an heritage monument. Qutub Minar is a towering 73 meter high tower built by
                                  Qutub-ud-Din Aibak in 1193.The tower was built to celebrate Muslim dominance in Delhi after the defeat
                                  of Delhi\’s last Hindu ruler.</string>
    <string name="LotusTemple">"Our next attraction -The Baha’I House of Worship, more popularly known as the Lotus Temple, owing to
                                  its shape and design, is one of Delhi\’s most recognized structures.The Lotus temple, constructed entirely
                                  out of white marble from Penteli mountain in Greece, the very same from which many ancient monuments and
                                  other Bahá\’í Houses of Worship are built."</string>
    <string name="IndiaGate">India Gate is a must visit on every tourist Delhi Sightseeing itinerary. Edwin Lutyens was the architect
                                of India Gate.Did you know it took ten years to be completed and it was culminated in 1931. It is said to
                                be inspired by the famous Arc de Triomphe in Paris.</string>
    <string name="RashtrapatiBhawan">Our next destination, is the Rashtrapati Bhavan or the President\’s House. The main palace building
                                was formerly known as Viceroy’s House.  The famous rose garden better  known as the Mughal Gardens is located
                                inside the Rashtrapati Bhawan.</string>
    <string name="GurudwaraBanglaSahib">It is the most prominent Sikh gurdwara, or Sikh house of worship, known for its association with the
                                eighth Sikh Guru, Guru Har Krishan.</string>
    <string name="Akshardham">Akshardham Temple in Delhi is undoubtedly the best place to visit in Delhi for tourists, heralded by the Guinness
                              World Record as the World\’s Largest Comprehensive Hindu Temple.</string>


    <!--banglore details!-->
    <string name="Jawaharlal_Nehru_Planetarium"> One of the main attractions here in Bangalore is the famous Jawaharlal Nehru Planetarium.
                             It planetarium has a Science Park and the Science Center. The most well known show in the Jawaharlal Nehru Planetarium
                             that pulls lakhs of people round the year is the Sky Theater. </string>
    <string name="Bannerghatta_National_Park">Bannerghetta national Park is another attraction which is a must visit for you. If you are an animal
                             lover than this park will definitely make your vacation a lot more amazing. Holding some of the country\’s first butterfly
                             park, this national park has a huge variety of fauna, making it one of the most enjoyable tourist attractions in the city. </string>
    <string name="Nandi_Hills">As the name goes this is one of the most popular attractions in Bangalore which is known for offering the spectacular sunrise from the top.
                              Nandi Hills, otherwise called Nandidurg or Nandi Betta is an old slope fortification arranged in a region called Chikkabalapur in Karnataka.
                              Arranged close to the town of Nandi, the antiquated conviction is that they are the cause of the Arkavathy River. </string>
    <string name="Cubbon_Park">Having been set around Lord Cubbon, it is a perfect place for nature significant others and those looking for a quiet climate.
                               It highlights a bandstand that hosts shows. The Bangalore Aquarium is likewise arranged in this park, and is a must visit for
                               you in Bengaluru, being the second biggest aquarium in India. </string>
    <string name="Vidhana_Soudha">Vidhana Soudha is a standout building among the very famous Buildings in Bangalore. The 46-meter tall building includes 300
                               rooms, each of which mirrors the noteworthy Dravidian style of engineering. Housing 22 departments  of the Government of Karnataka,
                               Vidhan Soudha additionally happens to be one of the one of the biggest authoritative structures and is a must visit spot in Bangalore. </string>
    <string name="Bangalore_Palace">Encased by beautiful garden, Bangalore Palace draws in sightseers in great numbers but also as a destination for important events and cultural
                               programs. The wooden structure of the palace with impressive carvings both inside and outside delineating distinctive building styles, is reminiscent
                               of the royal culture during that time.</string>
    <string name="Brigade_Road">Brigade road is the most happening part of the city. If you are new to Bangalore then this place is a must visit for you. From pubs to the latest branded
                               shop you will find everything at this place. Brigade Road is another famous shopping centre, particularly with the youths. </string>
    <string name="BigBull_Temple">The Bull Temple is one of the oldest temples in Bangalore built in 1537, amid the time of Kempe Gowda, who is known as the founder of Bangalore. The tmepls
                                is situated in Basavanagudi region, whose name came as a result of the sanctuary itself. </string>

    <string name="about"> Travel guide is an android application developed in 2018 to help travellers in exploring
                         a new place without assistance. This application will act as your guide throughout your
                         journey. It has a map to show you path when you are lost. It has a translator to get you
                         out if language dilemma. It has travel expenditure details to track your budget.
                         It ll also find you the best vacation spots in your dream city.</string>
    <string name="about1"> Travel guide is an android application to help travellers in exploring
                         a new place without assistance. This application will act as your guide throughout your
                         journey. It has a map to show you path when you are lost. It has a translator to get you
                         out if language dilemma. It has travel expenditure details to track your budget.
                         It ll also find you the best vacation spots in your dream city.</string>
    <string name="mapview1">
                    A  map is a visual representation of an entire area or a part of an areaa,typically represent on a flat surface.
                    Here included the shortest path in between teo places and also to know nearest  Schools,Restaurants and Hospitals.
    </string>
    <string name="news">
                            The Travel Guide app is offering comprehensive and up-to-date information about a particular destination to the tourists.
                            This information would includes popular modes of local transport,events and any other celebrations occurring around the places etc.
        
    </string>
    <string name="weather">
                        The Travel Guide app provides detailed local forecast and temperature ,rain or snow,windy,clouds,humidity,waves etc.
                        So it easy to receive the weather conditions in the current location.
        
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>


</resources>
